The answer is that in Sibiu, the action function gives us four actions
答案是 在锡比乌(Sibiu)(Sibiu)里 动作函数给出了四个行动
corresponding to traveling along these four roads.
对应四条路径
So we have to add in paths for each of those actions.
所以我们要把每个行动对应的路径加进边缘
One of those paths goes here.
一条到这里
The other path continues from Arad and goes out here.
一条从阿拉德(Arad)继续延伸到这里
The third path continues out here.
第三条继续延伸到这里
And then the fourth path goes from Arad to Sibiu,
第四条从阿拉德(Arad)到锡比乌(Sibiu)(Sibiu)
and then backtracks back to Arad.
然后又返回阿拉德(Arad)
Now, it may seem silly and redundant to have a path that starts in Arad,
看起来好像有点傻 也有点冗余 居然有一条路径从阿拉德(Arad)开始
goes to Sibiu, and returns to Arad.
走到锡比乌(Sibiu)(Sibiu) 又回到阿拉德(Arad)
How can that help us get to our destination in Bucharest?
这哪能帮我们到达目的地布加勒斯特呢？
But we can see, if we're dealing with a tree search,
但我们可以看到 如果我们用的是树搜索
why it's natural to have this type of formulation, and
就会自然而然地出现这种现象 这是为什么呢？
why the tree search doesn't even notice that it's backtracked.
为什么树搜索根本没有注意到这条路径折返了
What the tree search does is superimpose
树搜索会做的 其实是在
on top of a state space a tree of searches.
状态空间上叠加一层搜索树
And the trees looks like this.
叠加的树像这样
We start off in state A, and in state A, there were three actions.
从 A 状态开始 A 状态里有三个行动
So it gave us paths going to Z, S and T.
由此我们得到前往 Z、S 和 T 的路径
And from S, there were four actions.
从 S 开始 而 S 有四个行动
So that gave us paths going to O, F, R,
所以我们得到前往 O、F、R
and A, and then the tree would continue on from here.
和 A 的路径 然后树从这里继续往下
We take one of the next items, and we move it and continue on.
在接下来的元素里 我们选一个出来 从边缘中取出 然后继续下去
But notice that we return to the A state in the state space.
但要注意 虽然我们在状态空间里会返回到 A 状态
But in the tree, it's just another item in the tree.
但在树里 这不过是树的另一个元素而已
Now here's another representation of the search space.
这是搜索空间其它的内容
And what's happening is as we start to explore the state,
随着我们开始探索状态
we keep track of the Frontier.
我们会不断记录边缘
Which is the set of states that are at the ends of the paths that
也就是不断记录一系列位于路径末端
we haven't explored yet.
且尚未探索的状态
And behind that frontier is the set of the explored states and
而在边缘之后是已探索状态集
ahead of the frontier is the unexplored states.
在其前则是未探索状态集
Now the reason we keep track of the explored states is that
我们之所以要记录已探索状态
when we want to expand and we find a duplicate.
是因为当我们想扩展而且发现重复时
So say when we expand from here, if we pointed
比如说我们从这里开始扩展
back to state T, if we hadn't kept track of that,
如果指回 T 状态 而我们没有记录的话
we would have to add in a new state for T down here.
我们就得在这下面为 T 添加新状态了
But because we've already seen it,
可因为我们已经见过了 T 状态
we know that it is actually a regressive step into the already explored state.
我们知道这一步实际上折回了已探索状态
Now, because we've kept track of that, we don't need it anymore.
由于我们记录了这一点 所以就不再需要添加新状态了
[BLANK_AUDIO]
[空白音频]